翻譯: 可樂
你能不像趕牛一樣集合我們么
You can't round us up like cattle!
校對: 怪查理
Stuart去哪了
Where's Stuart?
他因為體力不支掉隊了
He peeled off back at the crick.
后期: 東仔
我去找那個掉隊的 咦嗬
I got myself a stray. Yee-haw!
壓制: 猴給力
我不管我們還有多少工作要完成
I don't care how much work we have to do.
我今晚一定要看奧斯卡頒獎
I am not going to miss the oscars tonight.
你知道么 我發現奧斯卡就是場毫無意義的比賽
You know, I find the oscars to be an empty competition
沒有一點藝術品格可言
completely devoid of artistic integrity.
Stuart
Stuart?
你是不是還在生氣<歲月驚濤>沒有獲獎這件事
Are you still angry that the prince of tides got snubbed?
芭芭拉史翠珊絕對應該拿獎
Babs deserved better.
為了證明我的觀點
And to prove my point,
我敢打賭你們沒人記得誰是去年的贏家
I bet none of you can remember what won last year.
<泰坦尼克號>
Titanic. Titanic. Titanic.
我的祖父其實有一張泰坦尼克號的船票
My great Uncle had a ticket on the Titanic, actually.
在最后一刻他決定不登船了
Last second he decided not to go on.
幸運的家伙
Wow. Lucky guy.
不 在回家的路上他被一輛送牛奶的卡車撞死了
No... no. On the way home he got hit by a milk truck.
如果當時他上了那條該死的船就好了
If only he'd gotten on that damn boat.
駕 快跑
Yah! Yah! Giddup! Giddup!
嘿 Mike 來告訴我們
Hey, Mike. Come on, tell us.
你在看<泰坦尼克號>時淚奔了么
Did you cry when you saw Titanic?
我從沒看過<泰坦尼克號>
I never saw Titanic.
這類電影不合我的口味
That's not my type of movie.
本組鏡頭出自于第三季第八集
我是副市長之王
I'm the deputy mayor of the world!
政界小人物
第三季 第二十集
電波誠譯
下個禮拜市長
Next week is the mayor's black
為外交使節團準備了一場正式的招待會
tie reception for the city's diplomatic corps.
這是一件大事 邀請函也就十分難以搞定
This is a major event, and invitations are hard to come by.
趕緊問我為什么
Somebody ask me why.
什么
What?
我勉強接受
Close enough.
它們之所以難搞定是因為
They're hard to come by because...
它們都在這個盒子里
They're in these boxes.
這三千封邀請函封上貼好郵票前
And we're going to stay here
誰也別想走人
till we stuff and stamp all 3,000 envelopes.
是哪個大混蛋害我的周末時光都浪費在這的
All right. Which one of these major jugheads cost me my Sunday?
Stacy你想讓我怎么做
What would you like me to do, Stacy?
你是想讓我
Would you like me to take
將那個傻貨叫到一邊 偷偷地告訴他們呢
that person aside and tell them gently in private
還是你想我在大庭廣眾之下喊出他的名字
or would you like me to spill it in front of the whole big group?
喊出來 喊出來
Big group! Big group!
就是你 Paul
It was you, Paul.
好吧 大伙們 如果我們手腳麻利
All right, you guys. If we work quickly,
還是能趕上看奧斯卡的
we can make it to the oscars.
讓我們來玩"根據臺詞猜電影"的游戲來打發時間吧
Let's play "Guess that movie quote" To pass the time.
太棒了 從我開始怎么樣
Oh, great. Yeah. I'll go first, ok?
<教父>中維托柯里昂的經典臺詞 由馬龍白蘭度扮演
我做了些什么
What have I done
讓你對我如此不屑一顧
to make you treat me so disrespectful?
首先 就是你這惡心人的模仿
Well, for starters, that impression.
我們能別搗亂然后把這些邀請函弄好么
Can we please stop screwing around and stuff these envelopes?
<野戰排>
Platoon.
我們不玩了 游戲結束了
We're not playing anymore. The game's over.
<夢幻之地>
Field of dreams.
如果你不立馬閉嘴 我就一拳打死你
James, If you don't shut up, I'm gonna punch you in the stomach.
<甘地傳>
Uh... Gandhi.
James你贏了 你就是猜電影小達人
You win, James. You are the king of movie quotes.
這些片段均出自于本劇 都用了電影橋段的梗
告訴他如果他再繼續這樣對我們糾纏不休
Tell him if he keeps yanking us at these things
他最好小心會橫尸街頭
he's gonna find himself on the street.
這家伙要么當敵人要么當朋友 沒得商量
The man's either with us or against us. Period.
Obi Mike把你教導的如此之好
Obi Mike has taught you well,
由Obi-Wan Kenobi名字改寫 星球大戰中盧克天行者的啟蒙導師
但是盧克 我才是你的親生父親
but, Luke, I am your father.
黑武士達斯維達 盧克天行者的親生父親
你們說不想讓我出現在那個同志大游行之上
Say you don't want me in that gay pride parade.
模仿<義海雄風>中經典的法庭對峙
但要我說的話
Well, I say, deep down,
你們從不敢言明其實內心深處
in places you don't talk about at parties,
你們想要我出現在游行的花車上
you want me on that float.
你們需要我站在那輛花車上
You need me on that float.
哦 這是我最喜歡的部分
Oh, this is my favorite part.
市長先生 我們只是需要一個簡單的
Sir, we're looking for a simple...
- 你想要答案  - 我認為我有這個權利
- you want answers?  - I think I'm entitled.
-你想要答案  - 我想要真相
- You want answers?  - I want the truth!
你無法承受真相的重量
You can't handle the truth!
我的馬丁尼酒 用搖的 別攪拌
I like my Martinis shaken, not stirred.
詹姆斯邦德的經典臺詞
這是阿爾帕西諾給我寫的推薦信
Here's one from Al Pacino.
你竟然有阿爾帕西諾給你寫的推薦信
You have a letter of recommendation from Al Pacino?
他就住在我家附近
He's from the neighborhood.
我妹妹跟他家的修理工有一腿
My sister fooled around with his mechanic.
她可真幸運
She is so lucky.
我太愛他在<聞香識女人>中的表演了
I loved him in scent of a woman.
吼哈
Hoo-ah! Yeah...
<聞香識女人>中阿爾帕西諾的口頭禪
吼哈哈
Hoo-ah! Hoo-ah!
Mike 我可真為你驕傲
Mike... Proud of ya.
模仿<甜心先生>中的經典片段
大家都這么說
This is what I hear.
我知道這可能聽起來有點愚蠢但是
I know it sounds silly, but,
我生長在一個沒有兄長的環境之中
uh, I grew up without an older brother
我的生命中需要一個令我敬佩的人存在
and I guess I need someone in my life to look up to.
Mike 正是你充實了我
Mike, you complete me.
James
James...
你說為我驕傲時就俘獲了我
You had me at "Proud".
Michael Flaherty
Michael Flaherty!
克里斯托弗洛伊德 與本劇主演狐貍叔合作過<回到未來>系列
Owen Kincaid 看看你 我告訴你
Owen Kincaid! Oh, look at you. I'll tell ya.
這一幕就像時光倒流
Uh, this is like stepping back in time.
過去的時光僅僅是我們人生的序章而已
The past is prologue, Michael.
像我們這樣的男人應當永遠著眼于
Men like us have to keep looking...
未來
To the future.
你說的是那種耍帥的憂傷是嗎
You... you mean "Sad" In a kind of cool way, right.
不是 是<星際迷航>大會上的那種憂傷
No, sad in a star trek convention kind of way.
模仿<星際迷航>中柯克艦長
Mike 你需要拓展你的眼界
Mike, you need... To explore new worlds.
探尋新的人生經歷
To... Investigate new experiences.
勇敢的走出這間辦公室
To boldly go away from the office
哪怕一天也是好的
for at least... One day.
我們會被抓個現行的
We're gonna get caught.
放心 今天是周日 市長完全不會察覺
Relax, it's Sunday. The mayor won't know squat.
他管理著世界上最繁華的城市卻沒有
How can you run the biggest city in the world and not have any...
找到了
Eureka.
Stuart
Stuart...
甘甜滑口
Smooth.
你到底怎么了
What is wrong with you?
Carter 如果你打算偷喝市長的威士忌
Carter, if you're going to steal the mayor's scotch,
最起碼該體面的用個杯子
at least have the decency to use a glass.
不是吧 Carter
Really, Carter.
市長先生您在這里做些什么
Mr. Mayor, what are you doing here?
好吧 我可是紐約的市長
Well, I'm the mayor of New York City,
城市不歇工作不止
the city that never sleeps. My work is never done.
開個玩笑而已
Just kidding.
我把<電視指南>落在這里了
I left my TV guide.
你想參加我們的奧斯卡獎池競猜活動么
Hey, you wanna join our office Oscar pool?
- 10美元  - 喂 你可收了我20美元
- 10 bucks.  - Hey, you charged me 20.
那是因為你有得天獨厚的優勢
You have an advantage.
你可是唯一一個會擁有
You're the only one who's going to get
花哨的基佬分類手冊的人
the fruity categories like costume design.
這個根本就
Well, that is just...
好吧 確實挺公平的
actually, that's kind of fair.
Carter你知道么 我敢說你一定同意我說的
You know what I'd bet you'd agree with me on, Carter?
歌舞片真是越來越少了
They don't make enough movie musicals anymore.
市長先生 你這難道不是對基佬們的刻板印象么
Sir, isn't that sort of a stereotype?
基佬就一定熱愛華麗的歌舞劇
The gay man loves the big musical?
而且 自從<雨中曲>之后
Besides, there hasn't been a decent movie musical
就再也沒有好的歌舞片出現過
since singing in the rain.
哦 <窈窕淑女>除外
Oh, and my fair lady.
<奧克拉荷馬>還是可以博人一笑的
Oh, and Oklahoma is just plain fun.
還有<西區故事> 不得不說是經典
And West Side story? Let's face it... classic.
抱歉如果我冒犯了你
Sorry if I offended you.
嗨 我親愛的市民們
Hey, there, citizens.
你們好 好啊
Hey, there... Hey, there...
歌舞劇<睡衣仙舞>中經典歌曲<Hey There>
- 先生  - 怎么了
- Sir?  - What?
市長先生 我們在直播中
Sir, we're live.
現在有請市長
And now, here's the mayor.
*嗒嗒嗒嗷喲*
*Da-a-a-a-a-ay... oh yo*
本橋段出自第三季第十一集
*嗒嗒嗒喲*
*Da-a-a-a-a-ay... yo*
先生我的麥克風出了點問題
Sir, there's something wrong with my Mike.
*來吧 理貨員先生 給我來一串香蕉吧*
*Come, Mr. Tally man, tally me bananas*
*白晝來臨我要回家了*
*Daylight come and me wanna go home*
*6 7 8 腳印一串串
*6-foot, 7-foot, 8-foot*
*白晝來臨我要回家了*
*Daylight come and me wanna go home*
那你趕緊回家吧
So, why don't ya
*Bill Bailey請你快回來吧*
*Bill Bailey won't ya please come*
這段也是出自第三季第十一集
*Bill Bailey請你快回來吧*
*Bill Bailey won't ya please come*
*Bill Bailey請你快快*
*Bill Bailey won't ya Please... Come... *
*回家吧*
*Ho-o-o-o-ome*
謝謝 我們會聯系你的
Thank you. We'll be in touch
在我后面可要祝你好運了 菜鳥
Good luck following that, junior.
你來自哪里
So, where ya from?
呃 你的辦公室
Uh... The office.
你是做什么的
And what do you do?
我是你的演講撰稿人
I'm your speech writer.
我是問你在這要做什么
I mean here.
你準備為我們帶來什么曲目
What are you gonna do for us here?
我準備演唱<丹尼男孩>
I'm gonna be singing Danny boy.
此處掌聲不能停!!!
你已經盡力了 小子
Well, you gave it your best shot, kid.
好了 現在我手中是最后一封邀請函了
Ok, I hold in my hand the last of the envelopes.
舔一下信封吧
If you would lick this.
哦不不不 我可不會再上當了
Oh, no, no, no. I'm not falling for that again.
James 你來吧
James, all you.
不好意思 我口干舌燥舔不了
I'm sorry. I've got nothing left.
來一口檸檬汁吧
Have a little shot of lemonade.
謝謝 伙計
Thanks, man.
啊 天哪 舌頭被紙劃破了
Ah! Oh, God, paper cuts on the tongue!
好的 搞定
A-a-a-a-a-all righty, then.
好了 我們可以走人了
There we go. We are outta here.
太好了
Yes! Yeah!
Paul 起來 我們可以走了
Paul, come on. We're free to go.
哦 我可不著急回去
Oh, I'm not in a hurry.
你看 今晚是我們家的家庭雜務之夜
See, tonight is chore night at the lassiter house.
今晚我要洗盤子 扔垃圾
Tonight I do the dishes, take out the garbage,
和Claudia做愛
make love to Claudia.
Paul 你在胡說些什么
Paul, what are you talking about?
不 這都是真的
No, it's true.
我確實得去扔垃圾
I have to take out the garbage.
你才剛剛結婚一年
You've only been married a year
你就已經了無性趣了
and you're already so blase about sex?
我還清楚的記得你和Claudia的第一次
I remember when you first were with Claudia.
你當時可是完全不同的調調
You sure did sing a different tune.
Stayin' Alive 電影<周末夜生活>中的歌曲
等等 你們要去哪
Whoa-ho, hey, hey, where's everyone going
我還沒交我的奧斯卡選票呢
I haven't turned in my Oscar ballot yet.
你投給了湯姆漢克斯 先生
Oh, you voted for Tom Hanks, sir.
是的
Yes.
在每個獎項上都投給了他
In every category.
我喜歡湯姆漢克斯
I like tom Hanks.
其余的選票在哪兒
Where are the rest ballots?
放在那盒子上面了
They're on top of those things.
跟邀請函一起放進信封里那些嗎
The invitation things that we stuffed inside these envelopes?
好吧 我們只好拆開找出來了
All right, let's start cracking these babies open.
有什么大不了的 不過是幾個外交官
What's the big deal? A few diplomats
在他的邀請函里夾著張奧斯卡選票
get an Oscar ballot in their invitation.
事可大了
What's the big deal?
受邀人可是一些外交官們
A couple of diplomats,
幾個外國使節 還有個大主教
a couple of ambassadors, the archbishop.
Stuart最佳影片獎你投給了誰
Stuart, who'd you vote for best picture?
親手投給了
Write-in vote.
<精子情深>
Sperms of endearment.
惡搞<Terms of Endearment> <母女情深>
最佳肉體攝影片我也投給它了
It's also my pick for best skin-cinematography.
難以置信 Stuart 你真是個傻瓜
Unbelievable. Stuart... You idiot!
怎么了
What?
拜托了 你們沒人準備幫我么
Come on, guys. Aren't you even gonna help me?
沒人 Paul 這都是你自作自受
No, Paul. You must suffer.
Stacy 至少給我一個拆信刀吧
Stacy, could I at least have a letter opener?
沒問題
Sure.
你想讓我把它插進你的后腦勺還是雙眼之間
You want it in the back or between the eyes?
我不明白為什么我們要怪罪Paul
I don't know why we're taking it out on Paul
這事實上是Stuart的錯
If you think about it this is  really Stuart's fault.
沒錯 就是你 Stuart
Yeah, Stuart.
這是不是意味著我可以不用做這些了
Does this mean I can stop doing this?
當然不是
No!
我決定要開溜了
Well, you know, I think I'm gonna split.
搞得像我會傻到被它滑倒似的
Like I'd ever fall for that.
哦 啊啊啊啊
Oh-h-h-h-h-h!
這就是天有不測風云
Stuff like this actually happens.
我真喜歡這些鬧劇
I just love slapstick.
哇哦
Whoa!
盡在掌控之中
Under control.
張開
Open...
放進去
Insert...
舔一舔
Lick.
- 嘿 Stuart  - 噓
- Hey, Stuart?  - Shhhhhh.
她們在重新封信
They're resealing the envelopes.
張開
Open...
進去
Insert...
舔它
Lick.
你在跟我幻想一樣的事么
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
當然 真幸運這些是免郵費的
Yeah. We're lucky we get free postage.
你的人生真是無趣啊
It must be so dull to be you.
我也是有經驗的 我和一位熟女約會過
I have experiences. I dated an older woman.
好吧 你真是威武雄壯 菜鳥
Yeah, you're a real stud, junior.
電影<畢業生>中成熟女性角色 與男主角開展忘倫戀
她就像欲火焚身的魯賓遜太太一樣向你投懷送抱
She had to throw herself at you like some kind of Mrs. Robinson.
你有想過跟熟女約會么
Have you ever thought about dating an older woman?
就一次
Uh, just once.
不對 算是三次 霹靂嬌娃三人行
Well, 3 times... Charlie's angels.
James你身上有種莫名的氣質
I don't know what it is, James, but there's something...
讓你顯得飽經滄桑
something about you. You seem so... so old.
如此成熟
So mature.
也許是因為你教的是四年級的小學生
Maybe that's because you teach fourth grade.
James
James...
是時候我們該...
It's time I took a chance...
我想我應該走了
ok, I think I should be going.
James 怎么了 我們只是聊聊天而已
James, what's wrong? We're just talking.
求你了 Paterno女士
For Pete's sake, Ms. Paterno.
我知道你想要干什么
I know what's going on here, ok?
你讓我和你單獨呆在Mike的辦公室
You have me alone in Mike's office,
你鎖上門 讓我和你挨著坐
y-you close the door, you ask me to sit next to you.
那又怎樣
So?
電影<畢業生>中的橋段
Paterno女士 你是想要勾引我嗎
Ms. Paterno, are you trying to seduce me?
你知道我今晚希望哪部電影獲勝嗎
You know what movie I hope wins tonight?
<莎翁情史>
Shakespeare in love.
言情片而已
Chick flick.
恕我不能認同
I beg to differ.
這部電影巧妙地利用了虛實穿插的敘述手法
It's a deftly woven tapestry of fact and fiction,
講述了愛與失 猜忌與復仇的故事
of love and loss, of jealousy and revenge.
簡而言之 破爛言情片
In short... Chick flick.
沒有什么比一部老式愛情電影更經典了
Hey. There's nothing better than a good old-fashioned love story.
舔一下
Lick.
早上好Stacy 幫我個忙
Good morning, Stacy. Do me a favor.
Paul來了告訴我一聲
Let me know as soon as Paul gets in.
我還需要那個婚禮賓客的名單
Oh, and I need that list of wedding guests
馬上給我打出一份
typed up A.S.A.P.
Mike 我就快完事了
I'm almost done, Mike.
模仿電影<人鬼情未了> 歌曲<unchained melody>
Stacy
Stacy?
你還好嗎
You ok?
我只是 剛剛有點走神
Yeah, my... my mind was just wandering.
對了 我忘了 我還有個電話要打
Oh, I forgot. I gotta make a phone call.
不如你現在回家休息吧
why don't you take the rest of the day off?
做什么呢 Mike
And do what, Mike?
我也不太清楚
Oh, I don't know.
模仿電影<軍官與紳士> 歌曲<up where we belong>
Everybody Gets What They Deserve---The Churchills
我只是在這散步
I was just out walking
聽著 其實你說的對
Listen, you're absolutely right...
不 不 關于今天的事
no... no, about today...
我簡直不敢相信 我們總算弄完了
I can't believe it. We're finally done.
終于可以回家了
We can go home.
只要Paul不再出什么岔子
Ah, unless Paul screwed up again.
這話不對 你們應該時刻銘記
No... no... no, guys. You gotta remember.
我們是一個團隊 我們要彼此信任才對
We're a team. We gotta trust each other.
我一個小時前就讓Paul回家了
I sent Paul home an hour ago.
我可不敢再冒險了
I couldn't take the chance.
Joan rivers 美國喜劇明星 Molly Ringwald 美國女演員歌手
Joan Rivers正在采訪Molly Ringwald
Ok, Joan rivers is now talking to Molly ringwald,
我估計紅毯秀馬上就要結束了
so I guess we're pretty near the end of the pre-show.
那我們正好能在奧斯卡頒獎典禮開始前趕回家
We have just enough time to get home before the oscars start.
不如這樣
You know what,
為什么不干脆在我的辦公室一起看
Why doesn't everybody stay here and watch in my office?
這個主意可不怎么樣
Oh, this is really lame.
你知道要是有朋友約我出去我立馬就走吧
You realize if I had any friends I'd be out of here.
我去弄點零食來
I'll get some snacks.
- 沙發歸我  - 沒門
- I've got the couch.  - No, you don't.
- 那板凳歸我  - 休想
- I've got the chair.  - Uh-uh.
至少讓我坐在地板上
I've got the floor!
市長先生 你跟我們一起看嗎
Uh, sir? You in?
我當然一起 Mike 我們可是一個團隊
Oh, I'm in. We're a team, Mike,
就像<虎豹小霸王>里的主角們一樣
like butch Cassidy and the Sundance kid.
先生 你知道在電影的最后
Sir, you realize at the end of that movie
他們都被亂槍打死了吧
they were both riddled with bullets.
我腦海里的場景是
I was thinking of the time that they were...
他們被困在那個峭壁之頂的時候
that they were trapped up on top of that cliff
他們緊緊握住了彼此的手 然后一起跳了下去
and they held hands and they jumped off together.
Mike 把你的手給我
Gimme your hand, Mike.
因為我們是一個團隊 對嗎
Because we're a team, right, sir?
是因為我不擅長游泳
Because I'm not a strong swimmer.
跳 跳 跳下去
Jump! Jump! Jump!
不了 先生 一次就夠了
Oh, no, sir. Once is enough.
湯姆漢克斯加油
Go tom Hanks!
Mike 開始放了
Mike, it's starting.
Mike 快點來
Mike! Hurry up!
就算她是
So what if she's a...
體育畫報泳裝版面的封面女郎又怎么了
Sports illustrated swimsuit edition cover girl?
又不是叫你去登月
It's not like walking on the moon.
Mike
Mike?
"一個人的一小步"
One small step for man...
"卻是人類的..."
One giant...
哦 老天爺 感謝你如此厚待我
Oh, dear God, thank you.
"雄鷹已經著陸"
The eagle has landed.
電波字幕組 歡迎您的加入
官方網站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@電波字幕組